杰森:好吧,还有人再要一块鱼片吗?迈克,本,开萝尔.
Jason: All right, anybody for seconds of the fish sticks? Mike, Ben, Carol
麦琪:不,不!谢谢,我已经饱了.
Maggie: No, no, thank you.I'm full.
杰森:好吧,波纳,你还要来第三块吗?
Jason: All right, Boner, how about thirds?
波纳:你真是了解我,西沃医生.
Boner: Oh, you know me, Doctor Seaver.
麦琪:杰森,我们去跳舞吧,到时就把本寄在沙利文家.
Maggie: Jason, We have to drop Ben at the Sullivan's on the way to the dance.
本:我和臭虫在他家的车库里搭了个帐篷.
Ben: Me and stinky get a camp in his garage in a tent.
杰森:这听起来不错.
Jason: Hey, that sounds like a fun.
迈克:我还是没有明白你们为什么非得参加今晚的舞会.
Mike: Look, I still don't see why you guys have to chaperone this dance
tonight.
麦琪:我们说过要去的.
Maggie: Because we said we would.
迈克:怎么非要参加呢?
Mike: Oh, Who needs Chaperones?
我是指德文伊中学的舞会实在是太糟糕了.
I mean Dewey High dances are boring nerd festivals.
开萝尔:我要和德布伊,雪莉一起去跳舞.
Carol: Oh, Debbie and Shirley.We're riding to the dance together.
迈克:被我言中啦!
Mike: Like I said.
开萝尔:给我闭嘴!迈克.
Carol: Shut up, Mike.
麦琪:迈克,既然舞会这么差,那你为什么每次都还要去呢?
Maggie: Mike, if these dances are so bad, why do you always go?
迈克:因为要是这次不去的话,可能会错过好东西的.
Mike: Because the one time that I don't, something great is going to happen.
波纳:是的,例如女孩在打架并把彼此的衣服撕下来.
Boner: Yeah, like girls getting into fight, ripping each other's clothes off.
麦琪:本,
Maggie: Ben, promise me you won't do anything embarrassing at the Sullivan's
你得向我保证今晚会安安稳稳地呆在沙利文家的.
tonight.
本:妈妈,和一个叫臭虫的人呆在一起会闯祸才怪呢!
Ben: Mom, you can't do anything embarrassing when you are with a kid named Stinky.
麦琪:好吧!
Maggie: All right.
安迪:西沃医生,
Andy: Doctor Seaver, Mrs.Seaver.
西沃太太,
Mike tells me you will be chaperoning our little soiree this evening.
迈克告诉我说你俩今晚会来我们的小舞会,
And I just want to thank you for taking the time,
现在我想谢谢你们能在百忙中抽空来参加.
out of your busy personal lives to be there for us.
杰森:那边见,安迪.
Jason: See you there, Andy.
安迪:西沃医生,那你小心开车.
Andy: Drive carefully, Doctor Seaver.
麦琪:再见,安迪
Maggie: Bye, Andy.
安迪:不能叫那几个中年人离开吗?
Andy: Couldn't talk the old stiffs out if this, huh?
迈克:不,根本不行.
Mike: No, not a chance.
安迪:迈克,别提这个舞会.今晚有一场精彩的电影,你知道吗?
Andy: Mike, let's forget this dance.It's going to be a zero, you know that.
迈克:不,不!
Mike: Oh, no, no, Andy, no way, man,
艾迪,我预感今晚会有精彩的事,
I got a feeling that something is going to happen tonight.All right?
肯定很精彩,我也不知如何解释.
Something big.Now, I don't know how to explain it.But I can just sense it.
不过我能感觉到,甚至能闻到气味.
I feel it.I can almost taste it.
波纳:那是鱼的声音.
Boner: It's the fish talking.
开萝尔:我很感谢你们能来和我一起去跳舞,
Carol: I just want to say how much I appreciated you guys going with me
因为今天晚上是我跟我男友分手后的第一次舞会.
to my first dance, well since I broke up with, with my guy.
德布伊:是鲍比吧!
Debbie: His name is Bobby.
开萝尔:我记得他的名字.
Carol: I remember his name.
雪莉:别紧张,鲍比晚上不会来得.
Shirley: And don't worry, I now for a fact Bobby won't be there.
开萝尔:太好了!
Carol: Oh, great.
雪莉:我听说他最近在和一个女大学生约会.
Shirley: I heard he is dating a college girl now.
开萝尔:谢谢.
Carol: Thanks.
雪莉:不管怎样还是欢迎你回到我们的单身队伍里来.
Shirley: Anyway, we're happy that you are back in the single life again
with us.
德布伊:可以一起吃零食.
Debbie: Eating between-meals.
雪莉:没事可以找几个年轻的男生玩玩.
Shirley: Looking for guys with buns so tight you could bounce quarters
off them.
开萝尔:也许我还没准备好这样做.
Carol: Maybe I am not ready for this.
德布伊:没有准备好?开萝尔,你总得开开心心的生活下去呀!
Debbie: Not ready?Carol, you've got to get on the business of living.
雪莉:包括准备去这些糟糕的舞会,
Shirley: And that includes going to dumb dances,
有人还会趁机和你亲热一下呢.
and get groped in the dark by guys with major zits and bad breath.
德布伊:还有那些浑身是汗的傻小子会搂着你跳贴面舞.
Debbie: Adolescent jerks pressing their sweaty swelling bodies against ours.
雪莉:女孩们,都准备好了吗?
Shirley: Ready Girls?
德布伊:好了,走吧!
Debbie: Ready, That's all.
迈克:女士们,你们今晚看上去真是性感.对吧,安迪?
Mike: Ladies.You all looking very hot tonight.Right, Andy?
安迪:真是美极了,是吧,波纳?
Andy: Red hot, right, Boner?
波纳:只有两个很美.
Boner: Two of them do.
迈克:他是开玩笑的,
Mike: Ah, he is such a kidder.
不过我们在想要不要带Boner一起去?
Anyway, we were wondering since Andy only has a two seater,
因为艾迪的车只能坐两个人,
if Boner can get a lift with you guys to the dance.
雪莉:当然可以,只要他能当行李.
Shirley: Sure if he doesn't mind riding in the trunk.
波纳:你说我可以一起去?
Boner: Oh, do you mean it?
杰森:本,玩的开心点.
Jason: Have fun, Ben.
麦琪:记得换你的内衣.
Maggie: Don't forget to change your underwear.
本:再见,明早见!今晚就随我了.
Ben: Bye, see you in the morning.Tonight, I boogie.
臭虫:本?
Stinky: Ben?
本:臭虫?
Ben: Stinky?
臭虫:我和我妈说今晚住在你家,你记得吗?
Stinky: Shh, my mom thinks I'm staying in your house, remember?
本:当然记得,这是我的主意
Ben: Of course, I remember, it's my plan.
臭虫:你都准备好了没?
Stinky: You're ready?
本:是的!今晚我们都会成为大人物的.
Ben: Heck, yeah!This is going to be the night we become men.
本:走吧!
Ben: Let's go.
杰森:现在感觉又好像回到了我们的学生时代,不是吗?
Jason: Now that kind of takes you back, doesn't it?
麦琪:是的!我记得有一次返校舞会,那个放唱片的穿着一身怪衣服,我都不知怎么形容他有多么有趣.
Maggie: Well say.I remember this one home coming dance, there was this lame DJ with these tacky clothes.I mean, I cannot begin to describe how silly he was, he had...
音乐主播:嘿!爸爸妈妈们!你们好!插座在什么地方,是声内线,通电的.
DJ: Hey, Mommio, Daddio!Yeah- you!Where do I get my juice, my essence, power?
杰森:进来吧!插座在后面,对不起,你在这儿工作吗?
Jason: Well, come in, the plug is there back.Excuse me, do you work here?
老男人:不,玩钥匙是我的爱好.
Old Man: No, keys are my hobby.
麦琪:这人想找个插座口.
Maggie: This man needs to plug something in.
老男人:在后台.
Old Man: Back stage.
音乐主播:谢谢啦!伙计.
DJ: Gracias, Dude!
老男人:孩子们好!
Old Man: Ah, kids
杰森:我们在找其他家长.
Jason: We were looking for the other chaperone.
老男人:我猜你俩就是家长.
Old Man: I bet you are.
麦琪:我们原以为会有其他家长.
Maggie: We figured there'd be other parents here.
老男人:是的,也许会有的.
Old Man: Well, maybe there will be.
杰森:那老师有吗?
Jason: What about teachers?
老男人:也许会有的,我不知道.
Old Man: Might be some of those too, I don't know.
杰森:那么你是指……
Jason: So are you saying that...
老男人:不用担心,德文伊中学的舞会什么也不会发生的,
Old Man: Don't sweat it.
事实上这是最乏味的舞会.
Nothing much happens at Dewey Dances, basically they're nerd festivals.
音乐主播:同学们,今晚你们父母都会担心死的,因为我是魔鬼.欢迎男女学生们,欢迎你们,我的音乐能够夺走你的灵魂,能使你们疯狂.
DJ: That's right, kids it's your mommy and daddies worst night, the wailing wailer.Welcome
Dewey hooters and hooterettes to Motown Night!I've got tunes, I say I've got tunes
that'll your brain, and make you Marvin Gaye
安迪:你说你预感会有大事要发生!
Andy: You said you had a feeling that something big was going to happen.
音乐主播:现在我们开始吧!首先是我的几个好朋友,
DJ: Let's kick it off with a cut from some dear close personal friends
玛萨,范德拉俩兄弟想向你们给你们个警告.
of mine, Martha and and the Vandellas are giving you a warning!
雪莉:好吧,女孩们,我们现对一下我们的表.
Shirley: Ok, girls, let's synchronize our watches.
开萝尔:雪莉,你怎么把车停在黑糊糊的地方,
Carol: Shirley, why did you park in dark,
放在亮一点的地方不是更安全吗?
I mean there was a place right under the street light.It's safer.
雪莉:的确.
Shirley: Exactly.
开萝尔:我不太知道.
Carol: But I just don't understand.
德布伊:开萝尔,下面哪个词不同类:男人,跳舞,亲热,灯光?
Debbie: Carol, pick the word that doesn't belong, dance, dude, neck, lights
开萝尔:是,这些都是名词.
Carol: Well, they're all nouns.
雪莉和德布伊:哦……
Shirley and Debbie: Oh...
开萝尔:哇!
Carol: Wow.
安迪:精彩的要开始啦!
Andy: Now, this is big.
本:我向你保证,臭虫,什么也阻挡不了我们去那里.
Ben: I promise you, stinky, nothing is going to stop us from getting there.
臭虫:你听见了吗?
Stinky: Do you hear that?
本:我什么也没听到.
Ben: I didn't hear nothing.
臭虫:我们回去吧.
Stinky: Let's go back.
本:臭虫,我们是去一个其他孩子们没去过的地方,
Ben: Stinky, We are going to where no kid has gone before.
我们快溜出去吧!
We are coming out of there rich men.
臭虫:但是我听说有人在里面被杀.
Stinky: But I hear people get killed there.
本:不要担心啦!
Ben: Don't be such a scaredy-cat.
本:我看到了.
Ben: I see that.
臭虫:我什么也没看到.
Stinky: I don't see nothing.
库斯曼:本?我是库斯曼,
Koosman: Ben?It's Koosman, what are you doing out so late?
这么晚了你们在这里作什么?
What are you doing hugging that little boy?
你们父母知不知道你们这么老远跑到这里来?快进来吧!
You guys are pretty far from home for this late at night.Better get in.
本:好的,那我们走吧!
Ben: Yeah, we'll...go.
杰森:你去吧,什么?什么?麦琪,你去拉开他们.
Jason: Go ahead, What?What?Break them up.You do it, Maggie.
麦琪:杰森,还是你去吧!
Maggie: Jason, you do it.
杰森:我不去,太尴尬了.
Jason: I couldn't do it no, I'd feel arkward.
麦琪:要是开萝尔这样,你怎么看?
Maggie: How would you feel if that was her?
杰森:嘿嘿嘿!别这样了好吗?
Jason: Hey, hey, hey, come up for air, will you pal?
天哪,想不到我居然会做干这种事,我以前很讨厌其他家长这样干的.
Ha, I cannot believe I just did that.I used to hate parents that did that.
麦琪:我还是一样讨厌.
Maggie: I still do.
音乐主播:来吧,杜义的学生们,
DJ: All right, do easy, Dewettes,
让我们彻底疯狂,彻底的解放,
let's get completely crazy and find out who is who.
大家都叫嘀咕嘀咕,魔鬼.
And they call me -dig it- the wailer...
(音乐响起)
(music)
音乐主播:你叫什么?
DJ: What's your name?
跳舞女孩:拉托娅.
Dancing Girl: Latoya.
开萝尔:好像越来越好完了!
Carol: This is going to be fun.
德布伊:行了,我们还是离开吧,没个像样的.
Debbie: Please.Let's dust this place, go to a burger joint, and not eat anything
开萝尔:回去?
Carol: Go?
雪莉:听起来是个不错的建议,开萝尔?
Shirley: Sounds like a plan.Carol?
开萝尔:但你来的时候不是说这个舞会会很棒的吗?
Carol: But you said it was important to come to this dance!
德布伊:我是说过的,但现在我们得走了.
Debbie: It was?We did, and now we're out of here.
雪莉:哦,罗宾·罗斯曼这笨蛋过来了.
Shirley: Oh, here comes a that goofus-oid Robin Rossman.
罗宾·罗斯曼:嘿!姑娘们!
Robin Rossman: Hi, girls.
德布伊,开萝尔和雪莉:嘿!
Debbie, Carol and Shirley: Hi
罗宾·罗斯曼:可;开萝尔,可以和你跳个舞吗?
Robin Rossman: Carol, would you like to dancer?
开萝尔:当然可以!
Carol: Oh, that'll be great.
雪莉:对不起,我们都有人约了.
Shirley: Sorry, the girls all booked up.
开萝尔:我有吗?
Carol: I am?
雪莉:是的.
Shirley: You are.
罗宾·罗斯曼:还是要谢谢你.
Robin Rossman: Thanks anyway.
开萝尔:那你怎么办?
Carol: Why did you do that?
德布伊:因为我们不能让你去出洋相.
Debbie: Because someones got to see you don't make a fool out of yourself.
雪莉:即便你不考虑自己的形象,那也得考虑一下我们呀!
Shirley: Even if you don't care about your image, at least think about ours.
开萝尔:我只是想和那家伙去跳一下舞.
Carol: I was just going to dance with the guy.
德布伊:大部分男人都是三分钟热度.
Debbie: Major dudes at three o'clock.
雪莉:男人都是猪.
Shirley: Men are such phony pigs.
德布伊:他们只关心女孩的头发,化妆以及文胸的尺寸.
Debbie: All they care about is girls' hair, makeup and bra size.
安迪:迈克,迈克,迈克!你是对的,今晚是要有精彩的事.
Andy: Mike, Mike, Mike, You were right, about something big happening.
迈克:是吗?
Mike: Yeah?
安迪:那是莉塔·萨巴蒂尼.她是学校的校花,另外她还是拉丁俱乐部的会长.
Andy: There is Rita Sabatini.She is the only girl in the entire school who
is president of the Latin Club
迈克:挺有趣的!
Mike: Oh, funny.
音乐主播:嘿!你叫什么?
DJ: Hey, what's your name?
波纳:波纳……
Boner: Boner...
音乐主播:波纳……波纳……
DJ: Boner ..Boner...
音乐主播:那你叫什么?
DJ: what's your name?
波纳:告诉他,迈克.
Boner: Tell him, Mikey.
音乐主播:迈克……迈克.
DJ: Mikey...Mikey.
迈克:好吧,看来我是错的,今晚什么精彩的事也没有发生.
Mike: All right.I was wrong.Nothing special is going to happen tonight
安迪:我不知道,也许等会就有.
Andy: I don't know about that, I thought that was pretty special.
迈克:好吧!最后再问你一次,你会不会去?
Mike: Well, it's the last time I said.Are we out of here?
安迪:好吧!
Andy: All right!
波纳:好的,反正我快把鱼干吃完了.
Boner: Yeah, I was almost out of fish sticks, anyway.
安迪:你带了鱼干来的?
Andy: You brought 'em with you?
波纳:不用担心,我也带了口香糖.
Boner: Don't worry, I brought breath-mints, too!
迈克:上帝呀!
Mike: Lord, have mercy!
安迪:迈克.现在我们要不要走?迈克,有趣吗?
Andy: Mikey, we out of here or what? Mike, yo... fun?
本:再见,太谢谢你了!库斯曼先生.
Ben: Bye, Thanks again, Mr.Koosman.
库斯曼先生:孩子们,没关系!
Mr.Kooseman: My pleasure, boys.
臭虫:再见.
Stinky: Bye.
本:嘘……
Ben: Hush..!
臭虫:放松点,我来处理.
Stinky: Relax, I'll handle this!
本:闭嘴,臭虫.我们会办到的,你看车来了!太好了!
Ben: Shut up, Stinky.We'll make it.We got to!Well, the bus, perfect.
臭虫:这车是不是去我们要去的地方?
Stinky: Is this the bus going the way we are going?
本:相信我,臭虫!
Ben: Trust me, Stinky.I know all the stops.Hey, I got this far, didn't I?
我知道所有的车站点.嘿,我们已经上路了!
We're on the way now,
臭虫
Stinky.
臭虫:你说你知道所有的车站点.
Stinky: Thought you knew the stops.
本:这站我知道.
Ben: I know this one.
臭虫:"相信我,臭虫,相信我".
Stinky: "Trust me, Stinky, Trust me".
本:我们会有办法的,你有没有自行车?
Ben: Well, we'll still make it.I mean, you've got a bike, don't you?
臭虫:我和我妹妹都有.
Stinky: Sure mine and my sister's.
本:好的,我骑你的,你骑你……
Ben: Ok, I'll take yours and you can take your...
臭虫:嘿……我不想骑女孩的车.
Stinky: Hey...I don't ride girl's bikes.
本:听着臭虫,这我只说一次.,你不去就留在这里,我自己去.那样学校里的同学知道后,就不会再叫我小不点啦!
Ben: Listen, I am only going to say this once.You can stay if you
want, but I am going to that secret place.
That's right, tell everybody at school
and I don't want nobody to call me weeny, do you, Stinky
臭虫:小不点还算好的啦!
Stinky: Weeny would be an improvement.
本:花这么多钱又放弃的话太可惜啦!
Ben: I didn't bring my bankroll just to wimp out at the last minute.
你到底是男子汉还是小女孩?
Are you a man or a little girl?
臭虫:我是男子汉.
Stinky: A man.
本:那好,现在骑上你妹妹的车,我们走!
Ben: Ok, then, grab your sister's bike, and let's roll.
安迪:起先你要来,刚刚你就要走,现在你是不是又想留下来?
Andy: First you want to stay, then you want to split, now you want to stay again?
迈克:我想去找莉迪娅聊聊.
Mike: I've got to take my shot at Lidiya.
安迪:迈克,这可是体操队的明星,
Andy: Michael, This is Lidiya Shane, head of the Drill team,
我们的校花,
home-coming princess and property of the very large Mr.Bushnell Narosky.
同时也是风云人物布什内尔·纳罗斯基的女朋友.你不要对他有什么想法?
I say you got no shot here.
迈克:布什内尔和莉迪娅两个星期前已经分手了,现在是八点四十六,
Mike: Bushnell and Lidiya broke up exactly 2 weeks ago tonight.
还有九分钟就刚好两个星期.
Precisely 8:46 pm.So the waiting period is officially over in 9 minutes.
安迪:你的消息到时挺灵通的.
Andy: You do keep track of these things.
迈克:我们过去吧!那就是为什么晚上她一直独自一人的原因.
Mike: Just got out of here.That's why she is here all alone tonight.
安迪:西沃,你真是厉害!
Andy: Seaver, you are something.
迈克:不,
Mike: No, Man, she is something.
安迪,她才叫厉害呢!
That's something special I had a feeling about.
我对她有种特别的感觉,
Man, I have had my eyes on her since I first saw her,
从第一眼见到她以后,
Shake her pom-pons.
我就忘不了啦!我已经预感到今晚大事的,
I said something big is going to happen,
但没想到竟然会如此精彩.
but I had no idea it was going to be this big.
波纳:波纳……
Boner: Bo...Boner...
迈克:你看波纳也玩的很开心
Mike: See, Boner is having a good time.
安迪:是的,他甚至连手都忘了洗.
Andy: Yeah.Hey don't forget to wash your hand.
波纳:好吧!你叫什么?
Boner: All right.What's your name?
开萝尔:我还是不明白你们为什么就不同意我和罗宾·罗斯曼跳个舞?我二年级的时候就认识了他,他是国际象棋俱乐部的,人还挺好的.
Carol: I still don't understand why you didn't want me to dance with Robin Rossman.I have known him since the second grade.He is in the chess club.He is...
雪莉:开萝尔,
Shirley: Carol, Trust me.
相信我,错过这些人没什么可惜的,
These dances are something you missed,
你好歹要找些更好一点的.
because you went directly from from being dead to going steady.
开萝尔:你难道认为我……
Carol: you have a I...
雪莉:你怎么会知道其中的意思呢!
Shirley: How could you know what's what.now that you're a dud again?
德布伊,你到底想要干什么?
Debbie?What the heck are you doing there?
德布伊:等我一会,好吗?
Debbie: Give me a minute, Ok?
开萝尔:那我就不要跟任何人跳舞啦?
Carol: So I am not supposed to dance with anybody?
雪莉:跟那些人跳就不行.
Shirley: You are not supposed to dance with just anybody.
德布伊:你们觉得这怎么样?
Debbie: Well, what do you think?
开萝尔:你的肩膀原先不是要高些的吗?
Carol: Then your shoulders used to be higher?
德布伊:你难道没听过有人说:"快看那女孩的肩膀啊!"
Debbie: Have you ever heard a guy say "look at the set of shoulders on
that one?".
开萝尔:没听过,但是……
Carol: Well, no, but...
德布伊:我也没听过,现在我们去跳舞吧!
Debbie: Me either.Now, Let's party...
麦琪:杰森,你答应过迈克不跳舞的.
Maggie: Jason, you promised Mike.
杰森:好吧!
Jason: Ok!
麦琪:杰森?我没在跳,我只是在摇摇我的腰.
Maggie: Jason?I am not dancing, I am shaking my waists.
迈克:大家可以公平竞争莉迪娅·仙恩!好的,那就快去吧!
Mike: And...Mark!Lidiya Shane is fair game.Ok, Go!Go!Go!
安迪:快去吧!
Andy: Go go go.
波纳:迈克怎么不假思索就去了!
Boner: How Mike could do it without doubt!
音乐主播:好了!现在改变一下邀请的方式,换成女士邀请男士.
DJ: Alright, if you can't shove that last toe-tapper, You are really going to
groove now, 'cause this dance is -ladies choice
雪莉:我们过去吧!他们刚好和我们一样有三个人.
Shirley: Let's go, there's three of them and the three of us.
开萝尔:你们现在真的打算要跳跳舞?
Carol: You guys are actually goin to dance at this dance?
德布伊:我们来这里不就是为了跳舞吗?你也一起吧!
Debbie: Isn't that why we're here.?Hi, Dudes, you want to..
迪茨:抱歉,我们度有约了.
Diz: Sorry, we're all booked up.
德布伊:还是谢谢你!
Debbie: Thanks anyway.
雪莉:抱歉,我们都有约了,这听起来真是没有礼貌!
Shirley: Sorry, we're all booked up.Have you ever heard anything so rude?
德布伊:你难道见过向她这样的蠢货?
Debbie: Have you ever seen a bigger couple of phonies?
雪莉:行了,开萝尔,行了!
Shirley: Nice, Carol, Nice.
波纳:嘿!看那里.
Boner: Hi, there.
开萝尔:波纳,你来这里怎么不跳舞啊?
Carol: Hi, Boner.How comes you're not dancing?
波纳:我在跳呀!
Boner: I am
开萝尔:我是说你怎么没舞伴呀!
Carol: I mean with somebody.
波纳:我也不知道.
Boner: Well, I don't know.
波纳:那你怎么也没舞伴呢?
Boner: Why don't you?
开萝尔:没有理由.
Carol: No reason.
迈克:女士的选择,我都快闻到她的香味啦!
Mike: Lady's choice, I was close enough to smell her perfume.
莉塔:嘿!安迪,嘿!迈克.
Rita: Hi, Andy, hi, Mike.
安迪:莉塔·萨巴蒂尼,你的拉丁俱乐部怎么样?
Andy: Rita Sabatini, how the heck is Latin club?
莉塔:我不干了,我在学一门外语.
Rita: I quit.I am trying a different tongue.
你们不是来跳舞的吗?
So How comes you guys aren't dancing?
迈克:我们还没决定谁先跳!
Mike: Well, we can never decide who gets to lead.
安迪:迈克,好像有人叫你.
Andy: Michael, you are being paged.
迈克:叫我?好的.
Mike: Me?Yes...
安迪:迈克还真是厉害,不是吗?
Andy: Ah, Boy, that Seaver sure is something, isn't he?
莉塔:是的,你想跳舞吗?
Rita: Yeah, so you want to dance?
安迪:我想跳,但现在是该女士请的.我当然想跳!
Andy: I was going to, but this was lady's choice.Oh, oh, oh, yeah, sure.
莉塔:好的.
Rita: Ok.
驳岸:我会抽筋的,你怎么样?
Boner: The jerk, you know how?
开萝尔:我不会抽筋.
Carol: No.
波纳:学我跳吧,就是这样.
Boner: Just do what I do, that's it.
开萝尔:好呀!
Carol: yeah.
波纳:你的抽筋舞跳的真好!
Boner: Now I'm looking at a perfect jerk.
开萝尔:谢谢.
Carol: Oh, Thanks.
麦琪:你是不是想跳跳?
Maggie: So, you want to dance?
杰森:不!
Jason: No.
麦琪:来吧!
Maggie: Come on.
杰森:好的!
Jason: OK.
麦琪:不,我们到最后去
Maggie: No, behind the group.
音乐主播:哎哟……
DJ: OU...
杰森:怎么了?
Jason: What's wrong?
音乐主播:背有点抽筋,老是这样的,
DJ: Twitch back, goes out on me all the time, what is cool.
不过不要紧,现在不怎么痛啦!
I'm feeling no pain.
杰森:好啦,我是医生!
Jason: All right, I am a doctor.
音乐主播:你不要弄啦!我要去找我的推拿师.
DJ: Get out of town, dude!I need my Chiropractor!
麦琪:我能什么可以帮忙的吗?
Maggie: Is there anything I can do the help?
音乐主播:把音乐继续播着,不让没有音乐啦!
DJ: Yeah, keep the music going, baby, or I'm out of a gig.
麦琪:但我不知道怎么弄.
Maggie: But I don't know how to...
杰森:亲爱的,这不会太难的,不要担心啦!
Jason: Oh, honey.It shouldn't be too difficult to do, no offence.
麦琪:抱歉.
Maggie: Sorry.
开萝尔:我现在已经转校了.
Carol: Now, I have to transfer to another school.
波纳:那很好啊!给她个机会,让她试试.
Boner: Well, that is good.Just give her a chance.and you see.
迈克:安迪,莉迪娅真是太棒啦!
Mike: Andy, Lidiya is amazing.
安迪:她是在应付你的,你刚刚叫她出去她怎么说?
Andy: She should be illegal.What did she say when you asked her out?
迈克:事实上我还没跟她讲,
Mike: Well, I haven't actually talked to her yet, but see,
舞蹈就是很好的交流工具,
the body language out there was just so good.
所以我觉得没必要跟她讲太多话.
I figure why mess it up with actual words.
安迪:迈克不是就你一个人这么想的,丽达比过去更有趣和成熟啦!
Andy: Well you know Mike, you're not the only one.
她还掌握了两种语言.
You know Rita is a lot more interesting and mature, bilingual.
迈克:是吗?
Mike: Yeah.
安迪:我这不是在吹牛或是其他什么,我是想……
Andy: Well, I don't want to brag or anything, I think...
迈克:我知道你在想什么!哈哈!
Mike: I know what you think.Ha...
波纳:先生们?
Boner: Gentlemen?
迈克和安迪:什么?
Mike and Andy: What?
波纳:这样的,我今晚玩的真是开心!
Boner: Well, since you asked, I am doing quite well for myself this evening.
谢谢你们.
Thanks very much.
迈克:是吗?和谁?那个红头发的吗?
Mike: Yeah?Which one, the redhead?
波纳:不,是那边那个棕色头发的.
Boner: No, the Brunette over there.
迈克:那是棕色头发的是开萝尔.
Mike: The only Brunette I see over there is Carol.
波纳:我想她挺喜欢我的.
Boner: I think she kind of likes me.
迈克:你和我妹妹一起跳舞?
Mike: You danced with my sister?
迈克:你想怎么样?
Mike: Ewww.What have you been thinking?
安迪:平时我让迈克找女孩玩玩,
Andy: After telling Mike all those things that you expect from a girl,
现在你居然用到他妹妹身上了.
now you got the nerve to tell me you got the hots for his sister?
波纳:没有亲热,我们只是跳舞.
Boner: No hots, just dance.
迈克:这里有这么多的女孩,为什么你非得找开萝尔跳?
Mike: Why did you dance with Carol when there are real girls here to dance
with, eh
波纳:我和她跳得挺开心的,没人和她跳,我挺她可怜的.
Boner: We were just dancing, having a good time.I felt sorry for her.
迈克:不要和她跳啦!我看不下去啦!你明白吗?
Mike: Knock if off, Man.It gives me the creeps, you got it?
波纳:知道了.
Boner: I got it.
开萝尔:好了,我们只是……
Carol: Well, we were just...
雪莉:只是和他亲热吧?
Shirley: things are not just done.
德布伊:波纳还挺开心的.
Debbie: And Boner is one of them.
雪莉:这是怎么回事?
Shirley: What's the deal here?
德布伊:你在想什么?
Debbie: What were you thinking?
雪莉:是的,你在想什么?
Shirley: yeah.
开萝尔:我和他跳得挺开心的,没人和他跳,我觉得他挺可怜的.
Carol: We were just having a good...I guess... I felt sorry for him.
麦琪:对了,这曲子个很好,
Maggie: Well, that was the nice little ditty, Actually it was kind of pretty.
听听这节奏,简直美极了.现在再来支首歌,
See, that rhymes?Well.Here is another song and don't get me wrong.
但是得注意节奏,大家自由的跳吧
Let's boogie!
迈克:打扰啦!我想这支舞你是想和我跳吧!
Mike: Excuse me, I believe you are saving this dance for me.
我们还没相互认识一下呢!我叫迈克.
We haven't officially actually met yet.My name is Mike.
莉迪娅:我知道,我叫莉迪娅.
Lidiya: I know that, I am Lidiya.
迈克:太棒了,你怎么会那个?
Mike: That's great, how do you do that?
莉迪娅:会什么?
Lidiya: How can I do what?
你是想跳舞还是想聊天?
So you want to dance more, or do you want to talk?
迈克:想跳舞.
Mike: Dance.
波纳和开萝尔:哦!我已经累了.
Boner and Carol: Oh! I've been feeling kind of tired.
波纳和开萝尔:什么?
Boner and Carol: What?
波纳和开萝尔:也许以后我们该……
Boner and Carol: Maybe later we could just... Yeah.
波纳和开萝尔:是的.
Boner and Carol: Yeah.
本:他们会发生什么事呢?
Ben: So what the hecks going happen with all these people anyway?
迈克会不会和那个怪嗓子的姑娘交往?
Willl, Mike finds something to do with the girl with that weird voice.
我不知道.开萝尔还有胆再和波纳跳舞吗?
I should have known.Will Carol get the nerve to dance with boner again?
波纳又敢不敢请开萝尔跳?
Or even the other way around?
杰森:你想请这个女孩跳舞吗?
Jason: Well do you want to dance with this girl?
波纳:今晚是我玩的最开心的一次.
Boner: Well it was the only time I was having fun all night.
本:爸爸还放唱片了,他是个心理医生,
Ben: Will Dad get the chance to play DJ too which is really what he'd
怎么也会玩这个.
rather be than a psychiatrist.
杰森:传统上讲这份工作最好还是由男人来做.
Jason: It's just traditionally a man is traditionally the best person
for the job of DJ.
麦琪:杰森,你没和男人结婚这是太可惜了.
Maggie: Jason, it's too bad you're not married to guy.
本:不知道魔鬼还会吼叫吗?
Ben: Would the wailer live to wail again?
最重要的是看来这个星期这集不可能放的完.我和臭虫最后去了我们的秘密地点,
And most important of all,
也就是布莱基家,在那儿我们还可以再赌钱的,
and the story I didn't think got enough screen time this week.
可是我放弃了.
Stinky and I finally get to our secret destination,
00:23:20,100
Blackie's where you can gamble for real money.Oh, no, I gave it away.